Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
- Box: 116, Folder: 16 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 35: The New Labor Contract in the Bituminous Coal Industry, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 36: The New Industriesa Report by U.S. Steel, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Item 37: BusinessBig and SmallBuilt America, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Benjaminn F. Fairless. Address Given April 26-28, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Post-Mortem--Steel Bargaining, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By R. Heath Larry. April 14, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Business.Big and SmallBuilt America, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    Statement Given April 26-28, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Seizurethe New Push-Button Warfare on Business, Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
    By Clarence B. Randall. Address Given April 25, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: United States Steel's Resply to Demands of the United Steelworkers of America (CIO), Publication (Box 116, Folder 16)
- Box: 117, Folder: 1 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Certain Unique Aspect of the Amercan Economic System, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Bradford B. Smith. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Pertinent Facts About Business, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Irving S. Olds. Presented January 20, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Communication in United States Steel: what, when, where, why, how, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: BusinessBig and SmallBuilt America, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    April 26-28, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: What Kind of Aerica?, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Delivering the Goods, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: And be Neighbourly, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By J. Carlisle MacDonald. Remarks Made October 25, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Certain Unique Aspects of the American Economic System, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Deour Ahead, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given April 21, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Reaching the Purple Twilight, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Clifford F. Hood. Address Given April 10, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Business has a Mandate, too, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given December 15, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Can America Compete?, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given April 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Your Business and Mine, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Benjamin F. Franklin. Address Given November 16, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Passport to Progress, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given October 31, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Unwarranted Doubts, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given February 7, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Great Expectations, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given March 13, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Private Impact of Public Spending, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given September 29, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: U.S. Steel's Policies on Costs, Prices, Plants, Productivity: First Disclosure of Iron Ore Discovery in Venezuela, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Safety Program, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Billion Dollar Bundle, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given February 20, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Employee Manual of Information and Guidance, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Information about Forthcoming Negotiations, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Welcome to Gary Steel Works, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Mid-Century Miracle, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: What Price, Controls?, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Irving S. Olds. Address Given February 21, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Leaders for Leadership, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By David F. Austin. Remarks Given January 8, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Some Words to the Wise, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address GivenJune 8, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Make No Little Plans, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given May 30, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Statement by Roger M. Blough, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. Blough. April24, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Half a Century of United States Steel, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Learning to Multiply and to Divide, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given January 15, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Basic Facts About United States Steel: The Industrial Family That Serves the Nation, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    January 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: A Concept of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By John A. Stephens. Address Given October 14, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: The Tax Education of Mr. Jones, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Irving S. Olds. Address Given May 3, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Costing Economic Changes, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Enders M. Voorhees. Address Given November 13, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Insurance Benefits Plan for Participating Employees of United States Steel Corporation and Subsidiary Companies, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    March 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Meet the Press: America's Press Conference of the Air, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Irving S. Olds. March 31, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: The Boy Next Door, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: "ask and it shall be given you", Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given December 11, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Our Mutual Ends, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Irving S. Olds. Address Given October 19, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: The Steel Rush, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given October 19, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Dedication to Success, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given October 18, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: An Ounce of Independence, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. blough. Address Given June 11, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: R. Heath Larry, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By The Right to Manage. April 7, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Mature Collective Bargaining-Prospects and Problems, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By John A. Stephens. Address Given September 21 and 26, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: "Investing in Yourself", Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given August 27, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Closing the New Inflationary Gap, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Clifford F. Hood. Address Given August 16, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: When People Profit, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given January 31, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: A Wonderful Cash Business, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given October 2, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: MatureCollective Bargaining-Prospects and Problems, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 51: Whose Sacrifice?, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given November 15, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: An Ounce of Independence, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given June 11, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Detour Ahead, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 54: A Report to the Boss, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given September 14, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Research, Security and Progress, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Dr. r. E. Zimmerman. May 25, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Recession with Inflation, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address April 18, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: A Talk of Two Towns, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given April 17, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Birmingham--City of Destiny, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Irving S. Olds. November 26, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Revised and Additional Pages for Administration Manual--Supervisory, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    July 29, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Revised and Additional Pages for Administration Manual--Supervisory, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    June 15, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Development of Union Responsibility Through Management Effort, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By John A. Stephens. Address Given November 15, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Some Economic Aspects of the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    By Dr. R. E. Zimmerman. Adress Given May 20, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Revised and Additional Pagesfor Administration Manual--Supervisory, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    October 13, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Administration Manual Pages, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    May 18, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Revised and Additional Pages for Administration Manual--Supervisory, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    November 12, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Administration Manual Supervisory, Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Box: 117, Folder: 2 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of Committee of Stockholders of the United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: What the Steel Settlement Means to America, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    By Roger M. Blough. January 4, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Business Administration and Economics Vol. 7, No. 53: Post Mortem-Steel Bargaining, 1959, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    By R. Heath Larry. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The New Labor Contract in the Bituminous Coal Industry, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    July 17, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Statements of Steel Executives, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. January 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The U.S. Steel Quarterly Vol. 24, No. 3, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    August 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Contract Economic Gains Summary--United States Steel Corporation 1936-1958, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Whose Sacrifice?, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Quarterly Digest of Technical Papers Vol. 6, No. 4, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    October-December 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: No. 110 Experience With Incentive Wage Plans, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    By T. L. Carroll. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Last Offer for Strike Settlement on Which You May Vote by Secret ballot Sometime in January, 1960, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    January, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: United States Steel Replies to the Union Demand for a $2 a Day Wage Increase, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Invest and Progress, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given April 29, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The U.S. Steel Quarterly Vol. 28, No. 3, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    November 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Letter to Miss Shirley F. Harper, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    September 18, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Business Administration and Economics Vol. 6, No. 63: Maintenance Organization and Training, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    By C. F. McClurg. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Steel Wages, Prices and Reconversion, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. November 13, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: News Notice for release January 29, 1946, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: News Notice for release January 30, 1946, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: The Nation-Wide Steel Strike, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    January 25, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: United States Steel Corporation Letter to the Stockholders of United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: United States Steel's Reply to Demands of the United Steelworkers of America (CIO), Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Bulletin: Text of Mr. Fairless' Reply to President Truman, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    January 18, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Volume XV-1968: Annual Digest of Selected Technical Papers, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Volume XVI-1969: Digest of Selected Technical Papers, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: U.S. Steel Concludes Insurance and Pension Agreement with Union; Strike Ends, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. November 11, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Business Systems and Computer Services Catalog, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: No. 110 Experience with Incentive Wage Plans, Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
- Box: 117, Folder: 3 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Unwarranted Doubts, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: United States Steel Corporation: First Quarter Report 1978, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: US Steel News: 100 Years of ET Steel Masters, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    July-August 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Equal Employment Opportunity Affirmative Action Program, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    Revised August, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: United States Steel Foundation, Inc. New Notice for release May 5, 1961, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Your Business and Mine, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given November 16, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Basic Facts About U.S. Steel, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: The Unprofitable Puzzlement, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given February 1, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Industry's Directive for Transportation, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Clifford F. Hood. Address Given September 10, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Profit is Not Without Honor, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Clifford F. Hood. Address Given October 22, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Then and Now, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Dr. R. E. Zimmerman. June 28, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: What Price, Enough Steel?, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given May 7, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Mature Collective Bargaining-Prospects and Problems, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: The Shape of Things to Come, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Clifford F. Hood. Address Given March 1, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Profits--Concepts, Measurements and Functions, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Bradford B. Smith. Address Given October 19, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Defending Freedom with Freedom, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given February 19, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Trickle-Up Prescription, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Roger M. Blough. May 17, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Mature Collective Bargaining-Prospects and Problems, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: The Lost Medium of Exchange, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By David F. Austin. Address Given October 8, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: "In the Sweat of Thy Face", Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given October 21, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Marketing in United States Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Richard F. Sentner. August 16, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: How not to kill a flea, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given November 12, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Power to Destroy, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given October 30, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Wanted: A Better Way, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given September 10, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: The Great Mistake of Karl Marx, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Target for Termites, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given February 6, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: The Fourth Dimension, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Leslie B. Worthington. February 5, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: The Cost Facts of U.S. Steel, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given August 10, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: The End of an Era?, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given March 19, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: The Great Mistake of Karl Marx, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: The Thousand Miles of Lao-Tse, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Irving S. Olds. June 1, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: The Working Man's Best Friend, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given May 18, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: The Changing Transportation Scene, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By E. G. Plowman. Address Given December 4, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Don't Throttle the Private Works Program, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. October 28, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: The Steel Strike, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: Detour Ahead, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 37: Inflation As a Way of Life, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Roger M. Blough. Address Given November 9, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Inflation or Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Irving S. Olds. Address Given April 24, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: More than Bread Alone, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Clifford F. Hood. Address Given September 30, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: The Vanishing Incentives, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given June 8, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: "The Common Denominator", Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given June 14, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Our One Indespensable Weapon, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given February 11, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Our New Kind of Inflation, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Robert C. Tyson. Address Given May 16, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Dear Mr. Presidentan exchange of correspondence on steel prices betweenThe President of the United States and Roger M. Blough, Chairman of the Board of United States Steel, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 45: Live for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given June 10, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Our Privledged Millions, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 47: Our Period of Decision, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Clifford F. Hood. Address Given March 27, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Unchanging Tide, Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. Address Given January 28, 1954. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 4 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Remarks of Irving S. Olds at the Forty-Seventh Annual Meeting of Stockholders, Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    May 3, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Press Release No. 19 "Celler Answers Fairless", Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    October 26, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: U.S> Steel Concludes Insurance and Pension Agreement with Union; Strike Ends, Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Manual for the Prevention of Gas Incidents, Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    May, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: BusinessBig and SmallBuilt America, Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    By Benjamin F. Fairless. April 26-28, 1950. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 5 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: United States Steel and Carnegie Pension Fund: Pension Rules, Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
- Box: 117, Folder: 6 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Monopoly in the United States: Facts revealed by the TNEC Investigation, Publication (Box 117, Folder 6)
- Box: 117, Folder: 7 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Treasury Department Policy and Procedure for Handling Employee Grievances: Departmental and Service, Publication (Box 117, Folder 7)
    December 8, 1942. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 8 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Veterans Administration Manual: Personnel Handbook for Supervisors, Publication (Box 117, Folder 8)
    January 10, 1947. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 9 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Role of the Personnel Officer in a VA Field Station, Publication (Box 117, Folder 9)
    September 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee Training--for Whom and What Kind, Publication (Box 117, Folder 9)
    March, 1960. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 10 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: "Executive, Administrative, ProfessionalOutside Salesman" Redefined, Publication (Box 117, Folder 10)
    Effective October 24, 1940. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 11 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Basic Guide for Labor-Management Committees: Ways of Operating a Labor Management Production Committee, Publication (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: U.S. Labor Goes to War, Publication (Box 117, Folder 11)
    January 25, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Job Instructor Training, Publication (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: U.S. Labor Goes to War, Publication (Box 117, Folder 11)
    Revised May 1, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Training Within Industry Program, Publication (Box 117, Folder 11)
    January, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Progress Report, Publication (Box 117, Folder 11)
    Sept. 1941-Mar. 1942. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 12 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Activities of the War Manpower Commission, Publication (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Wartime Research Materials Developed by the War Manpower Commission, Publication (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Basic Manpower Materials World War II, Publication (Box 117, Folder 12)
- Box: 117, Folder: 13 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Navy Orders New 'Copters; Northwest Buys Six 747s, Publication (Box 117, Folder 13)
- Box: 117, Folder: 14 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Bureau of Industrial Relations: A New Service to Members, Publication (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Helpful Hints for Dealing with the Wage Problem: Second Edition, Publication (Box 117, Folder 14)
    January, 1920. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 15 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Summary Report: Committee on Salary Benefits 1976-1977 Academic Year, Publication (Box 117, Folder 15)
    1976-1977. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 16 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 1, No. 4, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    December, 1950. Item is in English.